Guide to the Ricardo Sánchez Papers, 1941-1995
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES VII: Publications by other authors.
  - Subseries #5. Rare and oversized newspapers
    - La Guardia (1976-1977) (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Hospitality (1987) (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Humanizarte (1987) (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Interracial Books for Children (1969-1970) (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - IXIM Notas Indigenas (1978) (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - L.A. Moritorium (1990) (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - L.A. Style (1990) (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Living Color (c. 1978) (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - El Maizal (1978) (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Mestizo (1974) (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - The Metro Times (Michiagan) (1990) (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - The Militant (1987) (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Muse (1980) (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - National Hispanic Reporter (1991) (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Nauvoo Expositor (1971) (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Network (1987) (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - New Life News (1981) (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Nexos (ed. Sánchez) (1982) (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - La Obra Periodística (1972) (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - La Onda (1977) (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - La Opinion del campo (1978) (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - La Opinion Cultural (1984) (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - La Opinion de Matamoros (1990) (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - El Paseno (1986) (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Poetry Flash (1990) (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - El Popo (1978) (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - The Prairie (1975) (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - El Pueblo (1981) (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Que Viva Dallas (1993) (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Ranger (Riverside High School) (1989) (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - RAYAS (Revolucion Artistica y Accion Social) (1978-1979) (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - El Renacimiento (1973-1977) (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Resistance (1978) (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Resolana (1989) (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Revista Rio Bravo (1988) (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Revolutionary Worker and Obrero Revolucionario (1987-1989) (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - The Richmond Chronicle (1969) (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - The Rocky Mountain Woman (1977) (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - The Round Up (New Mexico State University) (1973) (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Sí Magazín: The Spanglish Magazine (1993) (Box 93, Folder 1.1)
    - SOMART (1986) (Box 93, Folder 1.2)
    - Southeastern Log (Ketchikan, Alaska) (1979) (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Soy Yo (1978) (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Spotlight: Central Texas Entertainment Guide (1983) (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - The Starving Artist Times (1983-1984) (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Struggle! Voice of the Black Student-Worker (1971) (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Survival News (1987) (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - El Tecolote (1981-1982) (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Tenontzín (1984-1987) (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Forumeer Today (1986) (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - UWM Post (University of Wisconsin, Milwaulkee) (1977) (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - La Verdad (1975-1976) (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - La Verdad (Otero County American Club, Inc.) (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - El Visitante dominical (1978) (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - The Voice of the People/ La Voz del Pueblo (1976) (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Vortex: A Critical Review (1986) (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - La Voz Hispana de Colorado (1977) (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - La Voz de Texas (1975) (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Xhismearte (1981) (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Ya Mero! (1971) (Box 94, Folder 11)
- SERIES VIII: Photographs (c. 1940s-1990s).
  - Subseries #1. Various photographs, negatives, and slides
    - Miscellaneous negatives (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - photos pre-1960 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - photos pre-1960 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - photos pre-1960 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - photos pre-1960 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - photos pre-1960 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - photos pre-1960 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - photos (1959) (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - photos (1963) (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - photos (1967) (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - photos (1968) (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - photos (1969) (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - photos (1970) (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - photos (1971) (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - photos (1972) (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - photos (1973) (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - photos (1974) (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - photos (1975) (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - photos (1976) (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - photos (1977) (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - photos (1978) (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - photos (1979) (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - photos (1980) (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - photos (1981) (Box 95, Folder 24)
    - photos (1982) (Box 95, Folder 25)
    - photos (1983-1984) (Box 95, Folder 26)
    - photos (1985) (Box 95, Folder 27)
    - photos (1986) (Box 95, Folder 28)
    - photos (1987) (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - photos (1988) (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - photos (1989) (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - photos (1991) (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - photos (1992) (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - photos (1993) (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - photos (n.d.), University of Alaska at Juneau (1989?) (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - photos (n.d.), including paintings by Jim Valdez (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - photos (n.d.), the making of the film Entelequia (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - photos (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - photos (n.d.) Ku Klux Klan march (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - photos (n.d.) copies held by the Benso Latin American Collection, UT at Austin (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - slides, "Feb 79" (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - slides, "June 1985" (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - slides, "June 1985" (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - slides, "June 1985" (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - slides, "June 1985" (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - slides, "Encuentro de poetas del Mundo Latino" (1986) (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - slides, paintings (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - slides (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - slides of artwork (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - slides of murals (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - slides (n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - slides (n.d.) Carlos Rosas mural "Entelequia" (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - slides (n.d.) Sánchez readings in Berkeley, CA (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - slides, Sánchez family, "Shootout in the desert," El Paso Trip," "Cinco de Mayo" (1984, 1989, n.d.) (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Subseries #2. 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment 1989
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, negatives and copies of photos (1989) (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, negatives and copies of photos (1989) (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, copies of photos (1989) (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, photographs (1989) (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, slides (1989) (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, slides (1989) (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, slides (1989) (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Ricardo and Tere, 25th Anniversary Wedding Reenactment, slides (1989) (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Subseries #3. Scrapbooks
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 1-6 (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 7-12 (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 13-16 (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 17-22 (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 23-30 (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 31-39 (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, pp. 40-end (c. 1954-1963) (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook, photocopies of newspaper clippings (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - EMPTY FOLDER - original binding of Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez (ballet folklorico) scrapbook in box 100 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - scrapbook (c. 1969-1973) (Box 99, Folder 1)
      photos, clippings, postcards, poems, notes, etc includes one envelope of loose items originally at back of scrapbook
    - scrapbook, "Crossing Borders: Chicano Realities" (1992) (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Jim Valdez scrapbook with photocopies of clippings (1992) (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - original binding from Maria Teresa Silva Sánchez scrapbook (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Carlos Rosas scrapbook (Box 100, Folder 2)
      photos, clippings, drawings Adrian O. Bernal
- SERIES IX: Audiovisual materials.
  - Subseries #1. Video cassettes
    - R. Sánchez, América Cósmica Nov. 29, 92 Museum of Anthropology (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Channel 10 Nov. 26, 92 América Cósmica (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - A Response to American Me - Dr. Ricardo Sánchez Nephtalí de León [no copy] (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - American Studies (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Ricardo's Birthday Party (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - El Paso Community College Television Channel 23: Border Cantos (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - El Paso Community College Television Channel 23: Border Cantos TV show short 29 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Border Crossings 6/11 9:45 AM Wilson 333 (1) (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Border Crossings 6/11 9:45 AM Wilson 307 (2) (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Border Crossings 6/11 1:30 PM JT 225 (3) (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Border Crossings 6/11 1:30 PM JT 226 (4) (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Border Crossings 6/11 3:20 PM JT 226 (5) (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Border Crossings 6/11 3:20 PM JT 225 (6) (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Border Crossings 6/12 1:30-3:30 JT (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - WSU Presents Yolanda Broyles-Gonzales, 12 Jan 94 (Box 102, Folder 15.1)
    - Burroland Mural Dedication & Process (Box 102, Folder 15.2)
    - Cable 8 News Package of Ricardo Sánchez: Raw Footage of Interview (by Stacie Kern and Jen O'Connor) (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Cable 8 News Package [no copy] (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Canto Campesino A Tribute to Human Dignity The Legacy of César E. Chávez [no copy] (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Los Cantos Humanos 1/Right (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Channel 23 - El Paso, 29 Dec 92, El Show de René Cantú (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - March: Tribute to César Chávez, FRI 5:00 [no copy] (Box 103, Folder 21.1)
    - Marcha for César Chávez, May 93 WSU (Box 103, Folder 21.2)
    - Linda Chávez Response by R.S. (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Chicano St. Conference 11/16/91 #1 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - City Council Meeting July 31, 1990 Twelve Travelers Project (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Combine Poetry 11/19/92 (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Community Issues (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - 7/2/92: Final Session/Class, Summer Institute, Crossing Borders (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - "Crossing Borders" presents Los Cantos Humanos de Ricardo Sánchez, June 26, 1992 7:30 p.m. at Washington State University (tape 1) (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - "Crossing Borders" presents Los Cantos Humanos de Ricardo Sánchez, June 26, 1992 7:30 p.m. at Washington State University (tape 2) (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - A Cry for Freedom and Democracy [no copy] (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Dallas La Vida, Angela Kercharga, 24 July 94 [no copy] (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Dr. Ricardo Sánchez at the Dallas Public Library (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - unlabeled tape, probably related to the Dallas tapes [no copy] (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - unlabeled tape, probably related to the Dallas tapes [no copy] (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - "Dances of Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow" - Orchesis Concert 4/10/92, Washington State University, Wilhelmina O. Sarah-Clark, Advisor (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - Nephtalí de Leon Wednesday, March 3, 1993, Fine Arts Auditorium, 7 pm [no copy] (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Nephtalí de Leon - News (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Eagle-Visioned - Feathered Adobes (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - Entelequía (Box 105, Folder 39)
    - Entelequía - Mural 5 de Mayo 1989 2nd Barrio - Boys Club - El Paso (Box 105, Folder 40)
    - Chicano/a Community Empowement: Dr. Daniel Estrada 11 am Sat [no copy] (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - Auditorium Farm Workers, UFW General Session 3:30 Fri [no copy] (Box 105, Folder 42)
    - Freedom Outcry: A Salute to Chiapas [no copy] (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - El Paso Dec 28 91: Gene K [Wilson] (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Gloria left view Sat AM tape 1 (Box 105, Folder 45)
    - Gloria right view Sat AM tape 1 (Box 105, Folder 46)
    - Dr. Ricardo Sánchez: Talk to Granger Jr. / Sr. High School Assembly, Granger, WA 4/29/94 [no copy] (Box 105, Folder 47)
    - "El Grito de Dolores" An evening of Poetry in Moscow (ID), Celebration of Independence of Mexico, September 16, 1992, R. Sánchez, T. Sánchez, P. Duran, M. Lopez (Box 105, Folder 48)
    - "El Grito de Dolores" An evening of Poetry in Moscow (ID), Celebration of Independence of Mexico, September 16, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 49)
    - Guerrilla Poetry (Box 106, Folder 50)
    - Johnny Gi-tar Gutierrez, Ricardo Sánchez, Dr. Tamnat (Miracle) Tademe Beanery [no copy] (Box 106, Folder 51)
    - Johnny Gi-tar Gutierrez, Ricardo "Poet" Sánchez [no copy] (Box 106, Folder 52)
    - Kristine Hauge: "Theatre of the Oppressed" Performance [no copy] (Box 106, Folder 53)
    - Hi School Orientation Cub - 9 AM FRI Opening Session Tribute Broyles (Box 106, Folder 54)
    - Inside El Paso, taped 9/13/90 (Box 106, Folder 55)
    - Hal Marcus "El Mercado Juarez" TRT 14:00, English (Box 106, Folder 56)
    - 5 of May in Prison on TV (Box 106, Folder 57)
    - 16/9/92 Moscow Ricardo - Felipe (Box 106, Folder 58)
    - Moscow World Fest '94, June 12 [no copy] (Box 107, Folder 59)
    - Noche Cultural I [no copy] (Box 107, Folder 60)
    - Noche Cultural II [no copy] (Box 107, Folder 61)
    - Noche Cultural TAPE ONE (7a) (Box 107, Folder 62)
    - 6/11 Cub Aud 6 pm tape 1 (Noche Cultural) (Box 107, Folder 63)
    - Una Noche Cultural, June 11, 1993, Cub Auditorium (8) (Box 107, Folder 64)
    - Cub Aud PM tape 2 (Noche Cultural) (Box 107, Folder 65)
    - Grad Presentation, Noche Cultural, 93 [no copy] (Box 107, Folder 66)
    - Mago Orona Gandara, Cont. Chicano Lit (Box 107, Folder 67)
    - Mago Orona Gandara, WIDE, Cont. Chicano Lit. W MEN (Box 107, Folder 68)
    - Mago Orona Gandara, Art Workshop, 6/27/92 (Box 108, Folder 69)
    - Felipe Ortego y Gasca - Abelardo "Lalo" Delgado, SVHS - 1, Luncheon (Box 108, Folder 70)
    - Felipe Ortego y Gasca - Abelardo "Lalo" Delgado, SVHS - 2 G - 1 (Box 108, Folder 71)
    - Javier Pacheco on Chicano Music Borderlands conference, Saturday, June 27, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 72)
    - Palousian Poets, taped by Jacinto Sánchez (Box 108, Folder 73)
    - Palousian Poets I, Apr. 1, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 74)
    - Palousian Poets II, Apr. 1, 1992 (Box 108, Folder 75)
    - Palousian Poets, April 23, 1993, taped by Jacinto Sánchez (Box 108, Folder 76)
    - Palousian Poets II Present "A Noche of Poetical Culture -Buscando the hey" Recorded April 23, 1993 @ The Combine, Pullman WA - produced by Liza Case - TAPE #1 - Raw Footage for Stanford (Box 108, Folder 77)
    - Palousian Poets II Present "A Noche of Poetical Culture -Buscando the hey" Recorded April 23, 1993 @ The Combine, Pullman WA - produced by Liza Case - TAPE #2 - Raw Footage ("open mic" not included) for Stanford (Box 108, Folder 78)
    - Palousian Poets II Present "A Noche of Poetical Culture -Buscando the hey" Recorded April 23, 1993 @ The Combine, Pullman WA - produced by Liza Case - Master Dub for Stanford (Box 109, Folder 79)
    - Palousian Poets II Present "A Noche of Poetical Culture -Buscando the hey" Recorded April 23, 1993 @ The Combine, Pullman WA - produced by Liza Case - Master Dub for Ricardo Sánchez (Box 109, Folder 80)
    - Palousian Poets at Robinson Park 6/25/93, Recorded by Jacinto Sánchez (Box 109, Folder 81)
    - Palousian Poets III, 16 April 1994, Combine, Part 1 [no copy] (Box 109, Folder 82)
    - Palousian Poets III [no copy] (Box 109, Folder 83)
    - Paperbacks y más (Box 109, Folder 84)
    - Reading at Paperbacks y más [no copy] (Box 109, Folder 85)
    - "Poets of Tejas" June 1991 Salute Ricardo Sánchez (Box 109, Folder 86)
    - Ricardo Sánchez 5/14/94, Chicano Poet, Poetry Reading, Revolution Books, Seattle [no copy] (Box 109, Folder 87)
    - Ricardo's Universe 1& 2 (Box 109, Folder 88)
    - Ricardo Sánchez, Final Session, 6/27/92 (Box 110, Folder 89)
    - 1) Ricardo Sánchez 2) Javier Medina - Europa, Somewhere over the Rainbow, Ya lo que tu te vas, Blues (Box 110, Folder 90)
    - Dr. Sánchez (Box 110, Folder 91)
    - Semana de la Raza, March 92, WSU (Box 110, Folder 92)
    - "Tacoland Farewell" Tribute to Dr. Ricardo Sánchez, July 28,1988 (Box 110, Folder 93)
    - Teresa - R. Universe (Box 110, Folder 94)
    - TV23 EPPC, 30 minute show, Ric. Sánchez (Box 110, Folder 95)
    - J. Vargas program "¿Qué Pasa?" presents Ricardo Sánchez, Ph.D., 26 June 93 Spokane, WA (Box 110, Folder 96)
    - Wedding Rik-Ser with Rie Nakai, Summer 1992 (Box 110, Folder 97)
    - Women of Color, Noche Cultural, Washington State University (Box 110, Folder 98)
    - Women of Color Day, Feb. 28, 1993, WSU, Tere's Group (Box 111, Folder 99)
    - Senate Meeting, Nov. 18, 1993 (WSU) [no copy] (Box 111, Folder 100)
    - Faculty Senate, Oct. 23, 1993, NACS - N.W. (WSU) [no copy] (Box 111, Folder 101)
    - Yevtushenko & Sánchez, 2-5-94, Unedited Raw Footage [no copy] (Box 111, Folder 102)
    - WSU Presents Yevtushenko - Sánchez, 24 Feb 94, ch 10 [no copy] (Box 111, Folder 103)
    - Ricardo Sánchez YVCC 11/15/91 (Box 111, Folder 104)
    - Copies of Videos #1, 2, 4 & 5 (Box 111, Folder 999)
    - Copies of Videos #6, 8-16 (Box 112)
    - Copies of Videos #19, 20, 21.2, 22-28 (Box 113)
    - Copies of Videos #29, 35, 37-40, 44-46, 48 (Box 114)
    - Copies of Videos #49, 50, 55.1, 55.2, 56-58, 62-64 (Box 115)
    - Copies of Videos #65, 67-75 (Box 116)
    - Copies of Videos #76-81, 84, 86, 88, 89 (Box 117)
    - Copies of Videos #90, 92-99, 104 (Box 118)
  - Subseries #2. Audiocassettes
    - Act III scene 1 cont. 2, 3, 4 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Mi Amors Por Vida la Marcie y Chico Baby Paul Por Vida cob Safos 1974 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Joan Baez, Traffic; Gulf Winds, When the Eagle Flies (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - tape copied by Tony Baez via Noe Flores (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - KLO Radio Juan Balli and Dr. Ricardo Sánchez, April 2, 1978 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Bassiento Interview Tape 2; 2/17/81 Mgr (KTEP) Selection Com, Ricardo Sánchez (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - To Ricardo y Teresa Sánchez, un recuerdo de Adrian Bernal 5-19-85 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - To Mr. Sánchez, 8-19-84 Mrs. Catacalos, A. Bernal (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - 4/26/73 Board Meeting; 5/15/73 Board Meeting; SER #1 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Bribriesca (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - 4-18-87, Side B, This Tape Features Sarah & Tavon's Song, Stevie's Love Songs, & All My Love, "...Your Smile..." "...nothing means as much..." Love U Baby; Side B, ON THE CORNER rough verbal draft by Tavon Briggs 1987 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Canto Blue(s), A: 1st read; B (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Canto Blue(s), C: 1) Santos, 2) Notas; D: Love + Sex (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - [Canto Blue(s)], E: Movement, Being + Lib -->Frags, Bad Tape (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Winning Images (morning), R. Castilla (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Cesar Chavez at University of Cincinnatti, April 10, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Los Chicanos, Grabado el 25 de abril de 1986; Paso al aire el 28 de abril de 1986 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Los Chicanos, Grabado 4/25/86; Paso al aire 4/28/86 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Cinco de Mayo en la pinta (1993), May 1, 93, Pine Lodge Pre-Release Center, Medical Lake, Wash., part of 5th de Mayo Fest (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Civilization 11/21/73, LCC (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Colon - Miranda Doble Engeria (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Ricardo Sánchez Dangibfried KPFT Radio, Nov. 87 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Poem #] 312. Edge of Texas: The Castillas at Oraibi, interview, Ricardo Sánchez; 268. Chihuahua (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - 11 nov 89, Poem 269: Edge of Texas: Coronado, Ricardo Sánchez (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - El Paso Inside, KCOS Ch. 13, 17 Sept. 1990, Tony Pina, Rosa Guerrero, Ricardo Sánchez, 1/2 hour (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Espejos de Aztlan 12/17/88, Ricardo Sánchez entrevistado por Cecilio Garcia-Camarino, Albuquerque, NM (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Love songs mix tape by Sonia Espinosa (Box 119, Folder 27)
    - Sandra Esteves 31:10 / Simon Ortiz 27:30 (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - Sandra Esteves 31:10 / Simon Ortiz 27:30 (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Floricanto - Sánchez (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Phil George 5:10, 28:44; Jacobs 22:08 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Phil George 5:10, 28:44; Jacobs 22:08 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - UNFINISHED BUSINESS, Roxy Gordon (Box 119, Folder 33)
    - El Corrido De Cesar Chavez, Johnny Gi-Tar Gutierrez (Box 119, Folder 34)
    - Hard Steps (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - I Married an Angel (Box 119, Folder 36)
    - Idols of Fear (Box 119, Folder 37)
    - Julio Iglesias (Box 119, Folder 38)
    - Indian Readings & Poetry: "Sánchez"; Phil George 5:10; Phil George 28:44; Jacobs 22:08 (Box 120, Folder 39)
    - IWASAKI 30:16; Tony Parra 16:20, 15:30 (Box 120, Folder 40)
    - copy of message of Ricardo Sánchez to 9/9 & 9/10/89 mtg to plan a campaign to shut down IWS Concentration Camps (Box 120, Folder 41)
    - JB's Madness (Box 120, Folder 42)
    - Ken & Gene Live at GRINS 7-10-80 (Box 120, Folder 43)
    - 8/22/93 - Coverage on KPFT on morning news of press conference; 8/29/93 - interview on KPFT on Enfoque Latino Americans (Box 120, Folder 44)
    - Marion (Box 120, Folder 45)
    - Meet the Pigs (Box 120, Folder 46)
    - Cine [?] Mexico Jam 2, Dr. Ricardo Sánchez (Box 120, Folder 47)
    - New Moon (Box 120, Folder 48)
    - Javier Pacheco con el conjunto "Deep Tong" (Box 120, Folder 49)
    - Javier Pacheco (Box 120, Folder 50)
    - Soto 4:30; Joe Beuchal 6:00; Berssen Brugge 7:15; Javier Pacheco 34:00 (Box 120, Folder 51)
    - Soto 4:30; Joe Beuchal 6:00; Berssen Brugge 7:15; Javier Pacheco 34:00 (Box 120, Folder 52)
    - Paperbacks... y más. 8/17/87. To Ricardo Sánchez fro A. ber[nal] (Box 120, Folder 53)
    - Paperbacks... y más. (Box 120, Folder 54)
    - 6/15/86. Dr. R. Sánchez. Poet-Workers feel. Esp. e Ingles; 6/15/86. KXER entrevista. Javier Roman - Ricardo Sánchez (Box 120, Folder 55)
    - Poets in the Struggle, Kenneth Carroll (Box 120, Folder 56)
    - Poets in the Struggle, Kenneth Carroll (Box 120, Folder 57)
    - 12-15-85, Poets of Tejas, #1 (Box 120, Folder 58)
    - 12-15-85, Poets of Tejas, #2 (Box 120, Folder 59)